

# Afiq Hazim bin Hairul Mazhan

Dreaming to create some things that can bring happiness and joy to people is becoming a reality. Creating an IT product not only brings challenges to the me but also gives an opportunity to learn more about it. From a young age, the sense of motivation and passion always keeps me driving forward. Whether exploring unique opportunities, learning additional skills, or meeting new people, I bring these values to every experience throughout my life on a personal and professional level.

#### Contact

#### **Address**

71, Jalan T.T.J.S., 3/4, Taman Tuanku Jaafar, 71450, Senawang, Negeri Sembilan

#### **Phone**

(+60)1110632696

#### E-mail

afighazim26@gmail.com

## **Skills**

Unity (C#)	••••• Very Good
HTML, CSS,	●●●●○
JavaScript	Excellent
Graphic	●●●●●
design	Excellent
Flexible and Adaptable	Excellent
Decision-	●●●●○
Making	Very Good
Mechatronics	••••O
Program	Very Good

## **Work History**

2022-05

2022-01

## 2022-02 - Mechatronics Programmer

Ucetak.com, Taman Lavender Heights, Seremban, Negeri Sembilan

- Led projects of mechatronics and Internet of Things (IoT) development that use Arduino IDE software.
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment.
- Created Arduino programs (C++) for ESP32 as main microcontroller.
- Created mobile apps using Kodular app developer to communicate with Arduino program.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems for every project.
- Completed paperwork for better explanation about each project.
- Worked flexible hours across night, weekend and holiday shifts.

## 2021-08 - Mechatronics Programmer Intern

Ucetak.com, Taman Lavender Height, Seremban, Negeri Sembilan

- Created Arduino programs (C++) for ESP32 as main microcontroller.
- Created mobile apps using Kodular app developer to communicate with Arduino program.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems for every project.
- Completed paperwork for better explanation

#### **Software**

Blender Very Good Unity 3D Very Good Adobe Excellent Illustrator Adobe Very Good Photoshop Arduino IDE Very Good

Very Good

## Languages

Kodular App

Developer

English Very Good

Malay Excellent

- about each project.
- Worked flexible hours across night, weekend and holiday shifts.

#### Education

## Bachelor Of Computer Science (Multimedia Computing) With Honours

Universiti Tun Hussein Onn Malaysia - Batu Pahat, Johor, Malaysia

## **Accomplishments**

- First Class Degree Awards (CPA: 3.73)
- Publish my game, Multiverse Run on Google Apps Store.
- Publish my Final Year Project mobile game, Ocean Survive (Dugong Story) on Google Apps Store.
- Make an own local server for the IoT projects that use communication between Ubuntu Server and ESP32 microcontroller without Internet.